# AudioWatermarkDemo

Use LSB algorithm to insert secret message to audio file (*.WAV)

!!! IMPORTANT !!!

	* PHP version is 7. And you need to change PHP's config in "php.ini"
		upload_max_filesize = 50M
		post_max_size=50M
	when run.

	* Format of *.WAV file need to have Header, Subchunk1, Subchunk2, Subchunk3. Subchunk2 (SubchunkID = "LIST") is optional but I need it!!! Let's use demo file named "test.wav" in project's folder.

	* All audio files, which is uploaded to and downloaded from, are stored in my Google Drive (I used Google Drive API). You can change to your Google Drive by changing file called "service_account_keys.json" to your Service Account Keys JSON.

	* Because file size is large (30-40MB) so you should wait 2-3 mins before buy song completely. Thanks!
		
!!! IMPORTANT !!!


	Administrator:
		id: administrator
		pw: 1234567890

